I'm, can I um...
我能   额
-That's why is it breathing too much? -no .
-所以他才呼吸那么重么   -不是啦
Mom, um when um, is it rumbling?
妈咪   他会叫吗
No you can't feel it yet.
不   现在还听不到
My belly's not big enough yet.
肚肚还没那么大
It got long long time to wait till my belly gets out there.
还有好久才能听到他在叫
Is it really coming?
真的快了吧
Yeah, but not till after Christmas.
是吖   不过不会晚于圣诞节啦
Is it make? Is it really in there?
是怎么来的   真的在你肚肚里咩
Really in there now.
真的在我肚肚里
How he make that?
他是怎么来的呀
Um, me and Andy made it.
额   我和安迪造的呀
Why you made it?
为什么呀
Um... Because we did!
额   反正就有了啊
You're to be a big brother.
你就要当哥哥啦
Yes!
耶
Is it really in there?
真的在你肚肚里吗
It's really in there, I'm not kidding.
真的呀   我没骗你
I'm, I'm gonna look in... I'm gonna...
我要   我要看   我要
You won't be hearing anything just yet.
还听不到什么啦
-Not yet. -No, not for a long time.
-还不行呀   -对啊   还要好久哦
Alright.
好吧
Nor you will better see kicking there for a long time either.
也要等很久才能看到他踢我肚肚哦
Why are you doing that camera to me?
为什么你要把镜头对着我呀
Could see how happy you are, if you are happy or you are sad, are you happy?
因为我想录下你的反应啊   看看你是高兴还是不高兴   你高兴吗
Yeah.
是呀